thecookedpea.com 2018-08-23

# PRIVACY POLICY | The Cooked Pea

## THE COOKED PEA

### PRIVACY POLICY

_Last Modified: January 25, 2017_

**Privacy Statement**

This Privacy Policy applies to this website located at _http://www.thecookedpea.com_ (the “Web Site”), which is owned and operated by Web Value, Inc. d/b/a The Cooked Pea (“The Cooked Pea”, “we” or “us”). This Privacy Policy describes what information is collected by us from any user of the Web Site (collectively or individually “User(s),” “yourself,” “you”, or “your”), as well as our use and disclosure of that information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, as it acts as an official Terms of Use statement, which governs your use of the Web Site. Your use of our Web Site indicates to us that you have read and accepted our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

MINORS UNDER THE AGE OF 18 MUST NOT PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION, INCLUDING THEIR EMAIL ADDRESS, TO THE COOKED PEA. IF THE COOKED PEA IS NOTIFIED IT HAS PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT A MINOR UNDER THE AGE OF 18, THAT INFORMATION WILL BE PROMPTLY DELETED FROM OUR DATABASE.

**Applicability**

Please note that this Privacy Policy only applies to the Web Site owned and/or operated by, and upon which The Cooked Pea has placed a “link” which, when “clicked”, transfers you to this Privacy Policy. It is not applicable to any web sites which are not owned and operated by The Cooked Pea. While on our Web Site, you may encounter links to these other web sites or online materials. If you “click” on a link to such a third party, the “click” takes you off our Web Site and transfers you to a third party’s web site, which is beyond The Cooked Pea’s control. These other web sites may set their own cookies, collect data, and/or have their own privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at the Web Site, and does not cover any information collected by any other web site. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any other web site you visit.

In addition, please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you may disclose publicly in any chat rooms, message boards, or similar web pages. You should keep in mind that whenever you publicly disclose information about yourself online – for example, via message boards or chat rooms – that information could be collected and used by people that you do not know. In addition, certain message boards and similar user forums may display IP addresses (as defined below) along with the message poster’s name and message. The Cooked Pea bears no responsibility for any action or policies of any third parties who collect any information users may disclose on the message boards, chat areas or other user forums, if any, on the Web Site.

**Information The Cooked Pea Collects**

**Personally Identifiable Information:** Personally identifiable information is information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally (such as your name, address, birth date or e-mail address), which we refer to in this Privacy Policy as “PII.” Generally, you may browse our Web Site without providing us with PII. However, there may be times when we ask you to provide us with certain PII, such as when you choose to register with our Web Site and/or for newsletters, or choose to participate in an online contest, sweepstakes, survey, or voting procedure. We may also ask you to provide us with demographic information or information regarding your interests, hobbies, or similar information. The Cooked Pea reserves the right, at any time, to add features to our Web Site that require you to register or otherwise provide PII, including credit card information, or to require registration to access our Web Site, or a portion of our Web Site. You can choose not to provide certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of, or participate in, some of the Web Site’s features. We may combine the information we collect with information available from other sources, including information received from promotional partners or other third parties. We may provide you the opportunity to e-mail a friend an article, electronic greeting card or other special feature from our Web Site. The e-mail addresses you supply us for those activities will be used to send the requested e-mail and will not be used to send you or your friend any other e-mail communications.

**The Web Site does not knowingly collect PII from children under thirteen (13) years of age:** This is not a web site directed to children under the age of 13, and The Cooked Pea does not knowingly collect any information from children under 13 years of age at the Web Site. If you are under 13 years of age, do not send any information about yourself to The Cooked Pea. If The Cooked Pea discovers that a child under the age of 13 has provided the Web Site with PII, The Cooked Pea will delete that child’s PII from its system.

**Anonymous Information:** When you visit the Web Site, our web servers automatically collect web site usage information. Web site usage information is anonymous information that describes how our visitors use and navigate our Web Site, and it includes the number and frequency of visitors to each web page and the length and depth of their stays. We collect the anonymous information automatically sent to us by your web browser, such as browser type, referrer data that identifies the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting our Web Site, and IP address. We also may determine what technology is available through your browser in order to serve you the most appropriate version of a web page. For example, we may determine that you have installed a version of Flash, and we will then send you the appropriate Flash version of the web page rather than an HTML page.

**IP Addresses:** An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer or network when you are on the Internet. When visitors request pages from our Web Site, our servers log the visitor’s IP address. We may collect IP addresses for a variety of internal purposes, such as system administration, to report aggregate information to our business partners or to audit the number of visits to different pages on our Web Site. Please note that some services within our Web Site, such as certain message boards, may display IP addresses along with the message poster’s name and message.

**Cookies:** Cookies are information files that our Web Site may place on your computer to provide extended functionality and to personalize your experience at our Web Site. We may use cookies for a number of purposes. For example, we may use cookies to track usage patterns on the Web Site and we may use cookies to serve relevant ads based on your expressed interests on websites within our network of online publishers. Or, we may use cookies to record registration and personalization information, enabling you to save your user name and password. We do not store any PII in cookies, but we may link the cookie to any information we collect. You can, of course, disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of the Web Site will not operate correctly if you disable cookies. You should consult with your browser’s provider/manufacturer if you have any questions regarding disabling cookies. To learn more about cookies in general, please visit [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).

To opt out of other ad networks that serve interest-based advertisements please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Targeted Ads:** When visiting a Web Site within our network, we may serve you targeted advertisements based upon information we collect about your past website browsing behavior. This information is used for serving you relevant advertisements only, and will not be sold to any third parties. The information we collect for serving targeted ads is not personally identifiable information and any information we store, will keep you anonymous. If you wish to opt out of targeted advertisements, please contact us by clicking the “contact us” link on the homepage of our website.

**Web Beacons:** A web beacon is programming code in a web page or email, which unobtrusively allows checking that a user has accessed the content. This technology can transfer an individual’s user identification to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about the individual. The Cooked Pea uses web beacons to track which websites you have visited and which advertisements you have viewed. Web beacons help determine products or services in which you may be interested and help track online behaviors for marketing purposes. More information about web beacons is available at <http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/W/Web_beacon.html>.

**The Cooked Pea’s Use and Disclosure of Collected Information**

**The Cooked Pea:** Information voluntarily provided to The Cooked Pea or lawfully obtained by The Cooked Pea is the property of The Cooked Pea and may be used for marketing purposes, which includes the sale, lease, or transfer of the information to third parties. We may also use your PII to contact you regarding your use of our Web Site or changes to our Privacy Policy, Terms of Use, or other policy or terms that affect you and your use of our Web Site. If you e-mail someone else an article, electronic greeting card, or other special feature from our Web Site, we will use the information you provide about someone else to send that person the requested e-mail. The Cooked Pea may use information collected about our users to improve the content and navigation of our Web Site, or for other internal purposes.

**Third parties providing services on our behalf:** The Cooked Pea may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on its behalf such as cookies and web beacons provided by third parties. Third parties placing advertisements on the Web Site may collect information about you, by using their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology. Third parties use of such technology is not under The Cooked Pea’s control. The Cooked Pea may place cookies of its advertisers who are under contract with The Cooked Pea on your computer. This technology may be placed within emails sent by The Cooked Pea or a third party, which you open or click to view. This Privacy Policy is not applicable to third parties that are not in contract with The Cooked Pea or to individuals with no affiliation to The Cooked Pea. Articles and email messages transmitted through email by The Cooked Pea on its own behalf or on behalf of content providers may have links to the third party websites. The Cooked Pea is only responsible for the privacy policy and practices of The Cooked Pea and is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices on any other websites.

**Other Third Parties:** The Cooked Pea may disclose anonymous, aggregated user statistics to third parties for a variety of purposes. For example, we may disclose how many individuals visited certain areas of our Web Site, or how many men or women receive our newsletter. The Cooked Pea does not rent, sell, or otherwise disclose your PII to third parties unless disclosed to you at the time such information is collected, or unless you otherwise give consent, other than in the following limited circumstances:

**Legal action:** The Cooked Pea may disclose information about its users, including PII, when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Web Site and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web Site. The Cooked Pea may also disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability, to protect or defend our rights or property or protect the safety, rights, or property of our users.

**Affiliated Companies and Corporate change:** The Cooked Pea may sell, transfer, or otherwise disclose user information, including PII, to wholly owned or controlled The Cooked Pea entities, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of substantially all assets, or other fundamental corporate change respecting the Web Site.

**Security:** The Cooked Pea takes steps to secure the data you submit to us, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our user data. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, The Cooked Pea cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to The Cooked Pea and you do so at your own risk. That said, all financial transactions, if any, completed through the Web Site use sophisticated e-commerce software and hardware.

**Consent to Transfer:** The Web Site is operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our Web Site, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

**Acceptance / Changes to Privacy Policy:** By using the Web Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. The Cooked Pea reserves the right to modify, alter, or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time in its sole discretion, with or without notice to you. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back from time to time. However, We will only use the PII you provide to the Web Site in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy, unless you give us your consent.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at the address provided on the The Cooked Pea homepage.
